module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'How do you spell what drummers have?', 
    a: 'Rhythm',
    b: 'Rhythym',
    c: 'Rythm',
    d: 'Rythym',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you spell something that is required to be done?', 
    a: 'Necessary',
    b: 'Neccessary',
    c: 'Necesary',
    d: 'Necissary',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you spell what Alfred Yankovic is?', 
    a: 'Weerd',
    b: 'Weird',
    c: 'Wierd',
    d: 'Weered',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you spell this place where we get buried?', 
    a: 'Cemetary',
    b: 'Simitary',
    c: 'Cimitary',
    d: 'Cemetery',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you spell the feeling you get when you check in late to trivia?', 
    a: 'Embarassed',
    b: 'Embaressed',
    c: 'Embarrassed',
    d: 'Embearessed',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you spell where Johnny Depp is a pirate?', 
    a: 'Caribbean',
    b: 'Caribean',
    c: 'Carribean',
    d: 'Carribbean',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you ____________ spelling this word?', 
    a: 'Recomend',
    b: 'Recommend',
    c: 'Reccommend',
    d: 'Reccomend',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you spell the thing that takes the place of something else?', 
    a: 'Supercede',
    b: 'Suprecede',
    c: 'Supreseed',
    d: 'Supersede',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you spell what Jiminy Cricket is to Pinocchio?', 
    a: 'Conscience',
    b: 'Consciense',
    c: 'Conscence',
    d: 'Conscious',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you spell what Robert Mueller is really good at doing?', 
    a: 'Indict',
    b: 'Endict',
    c: 'Indite',
    d: 'Endite',
    answer: 'a'
  },
];